

Yerevan, Armenia, +374 94 535279, grigori.aramyan@gmail.com

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Full Stack Developer with 10+ years experience in building scalable web applications and internal tools that drastically improve efficiency. I am self-motivated and self- taught professional who likes challenges. I merge a passion for usability and user experience with technical knowledge to create miscellaneous and atypical digital experiences. Throughout my career I have implemented more than 50 web applications and e-commerce.

#### **SKILLS**

- React
- PHP/Laravel
- Node/Express
- MySQL

- Vue
- Ruby/Rails
- PostgreSQL
- Github/Gitlab

- Vanilla JavaScript
- Python/Django
- Mongo

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Full Stack Developer January 2018 - Current

#### ArmCoding

- Designing user interactions of web pages.
- Creating servers and databases for functionality.
- Ensuring responsiveness of applications.
- Working alongside graphic designers for web design features.
- Leading a project from its conception to finished product.
- Designing and developing APIs.
- Taking care of meeting both technical and consumer needs.

## Full Stack Engineer October 2017 - April 2018

## Chit Learning (Armenian startup)

- Adapting websites to match changing user preferences and client demands with regular updates.
- Managing back-end requirements such as renewing domain name registrations.
- · Checking structure, conformance and browser compatibility of code with validation processes.

# Full Stack Web Engineer

July 2016 - April 2017

# Innovities (Armenian startup)

- UI development team lead (React, Redux)
- Developing back-end API with Ruby on Rails
- Designing and developing text analyzing ML models in Python
- Designing and developing new business idea generator ML models in Python.

## Full-Stack Web Engineer

January 2016 - July 2016

#### SKU Market (Russian startup)

- Designing UI/UX of pages
- Ensuring responsiveness Of UI
- Designing back-end architecture, database schema

• Ensuring integrity of bartering flow

Android developer

January 2015 - December 2015

# EatFully (UK startup)

- Developing and maintaining applications aimed at a vast number of diverse Android devices.
- Developing Android applications and their integration with back-end services
- Designing applications around natural user interfaces
- Converting business requirements into technical.

# **EDUCATION**

BA in Industrial Electronics June 2012

SEUA

Armenian Code Academy/Android Development

April 2014

# **INTERESTS**

Robotics: Robotics and IoT system construction Music: Music for high vibrations of the mind Poetry: For getting into different worlds Hiking: Passion for hiking and alpinism